

About Me

I am a frontend developer located in Myanmar and I have been studying web development since 2019.

I'm open to Job opportunities where I can contribute, learn and grow. If you have a good opportunity that matches my skills and experience then don't hesitate to contact me.



+959 770106619



htetmyataung16000@gmail.com



Yangon, Myanmar



https://www.linkedin.com/in/htetmyat-aung-hma



https://hma-portfolio.vercel.app

PERSONAL DETAIL

- Nationality Myanmar
- Date of Birth 2/3/2002
- Gender Male

EDUCATION

Yadanabon University Geography Major 2019

MST University
ITPEC (Information Technology)
2022

HTET MYAT AUNG

Software Developer

EXPERIENCES

IT CORNER Computer Training School Mandalay - Myanmar 2020 - 2022

During my tenure at the **IT CORNER**, I focused on both training and frontend web design for a span of two years. This involved developing training programs and designing user-friendly interfaces. I got a lot of experience at this work.

Freelance Yangon - Myanmar 2022 - 2023

During my one-year **freelance** journey, I engaged in collaborative efforts, effectively contributing to team projects while demonstrating strong teamwork skills. I actively collaborated with team members, effectively managing time to meet project deadlines and deliver quality results.

Innovix Solutions Yangon - Myanmar 2023 - 2024

During my tenure at **Innovix Solutions** company, I spearheaded the development of numerous dynamic and static websites, including government static sites, ecommerce platforms, chat web versions, online library websites, and more. These projects presented various challenges that I adeptly navigated, honing my problemsolving skills and enriching my experience.

EXPERTISES

- Management Skills
- Creativity
- Responsive Design
- Clean Code
- User Friendly UI
- Design Maintenance

LANGUAGES

- English (Intermediate)
- Burmese (native)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML.CSS
- SASS
- JavaScript, TypeScript
- Bootstrap & Tailwind css
- React Js & Next Js (others ecosystem)
- Figma, Adobe XD (design tools)
- Git & GitHub (VCS)
- Apis Integration
- Node js

INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

- Communication
- Active Listening
- Collaboration
- Conflict Resolution
- Emotional Intelligence
- Good at analytical skill, eager

CERTIFICATES

- Essential Digital Skills (NVL University)
- Web Development (NVL University)
- Special Web Design (MMSIT)

PROJECTS LISTS

- Pet Food Shop
- Online Library
- Community Chat
- Ecommerce
- Fake Commerce
- School Webiste
- Marketing Brand Website
- Government Booking Website
- Bank Webiste
- Foodie Website

PROJECTS SUMMARY

Pet Food Shop

Features

- User Authentication (B2B/B2C)
 (Login/Register/Logout/Forgot/Change)
- Product Lists
- Product Detail
- Add to cart
- Add to wishlist
- Order (Pickup/Delivary)
- About us . Contact
- User Profile and others

Tech Stack

- React Js
- Redux, Redux ToolKit (State Management)
- Tailwind css, Formik
- Odoo Api
- Bitbucket
- Jira Project Management

Online Library

Features

- User Authentication (Login)
- Book Lists / Author Lists
- Book Detail (PDF/Audio/Video File)
 (Download with request)
- Add to wishlist
- About us, Contact
- User Profile and others

Tech Stack

- React Js
- Redux, Redux ToolKit (State Management)
- Bootstrap, Sass
- Odoo Api
- Bitbucket
- Jira Project Management

Ecommerce

Features

- User Authentication
 (Login/Register/Logout/Forgot/Change)
- Product Lists. Product Detail
- Add to cart, Add to wishlist
- Order (Pickup/Delivary)
- About us . Contact
- User Profile and others

Tech Stack

- React Js
- Redux, Redux ToolKit
 (State Management)
- Bootstrap, Sass
- Odoo Api
- Bitbucket, Jira Project Management

Community Chat

Features

- User Authentication (Login)
- Create Channel, Create Group
- Send message / attachment file
- Group member mention
- Group member (Add/remove)
- Channel Member Detail
- User Profile and others

Tech Stack

- React Js
- Redux, Redux ToolKit
 (State Management)
- Tailwind css, Formik
- Firebase
- Odoo Api
- Bitbucket
- Jira Project Management